Devon Nathan

Developer

www.devonnathan.com devon.nathan@protonmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/devonnathan/ www.github.com/devon-n

WORK EXPERIENCE

Solidity Blockchain Developer

Level 77 - Blowfish Studios 2022 - 2024

- Layer Zero Omnichain Tokens & NFTs
- Dynamic NFTs
- Staking and Rewards
- Unity Blockchain Integration
- Gas Free Transactions
- Front End & Back End Blockchain Integration
- Flow Blockchain + Unity WebGL
- Upgradeable Smart Contracts

Substitute Instructor

2u Monash University 2022 - 2022

Taught Blockchain Programming and Al

Blockchain Developer

Panda Siege 2021 - 2022

- NFT Minting Dapp
- Multi-NFT Marketplace
- Generative NFTs

Full Stack Developer

Crypto Fund Me 2020 - 2021

- ENS Domain Deployment
- IPFS Hosted Website
- NFT Crowdfunding Platform

IT/Python Developer

Ecotec 2018-2021

- Data Collection
- Automated Reporting
- Computer Vision for Paperless Accounting

IT/Programmer Freelancer

2015 - 2018

- Genetic Algorithms for Game Development
- Automation (Reports, Emailing, Data Entry, etc.)

EDUCATION

Macquarie University 2019

Bachelor of Commerce Bachelor of Arts

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A driven and energetic programmer with experience in machine learning, neural networks and solidity smart contracts. I am extremely interested in what blockchain technology can do for the future of money and governance and enjoy contributing to the space.

SKILLS

Blockchain

- · Solidity, Geth, Ganache-CLI
- · Foundry, Truffle, Hardhat

Python

- Python, Brownie, Web3py
- Keras, HyperNEAT, SciKitLearn
- Computer Vision

Javascript/Typescript

- Node
- Express
- EthersJS, Web3JS
- React, NEXTjs

ΑI

- Machine Learning
- Neural Networks
- Genetic Algorithms
- Neuroevolution of Augmenting Topologies

Gaming

- Unity
- C#

Julia

CI/CD

Github CI

OWN PROJECTS

- MLB & NBA AI Betting Predictor
- · Greyhound Racing Predictor
- Defi Portfolio Balancer
- CEX Futures Bot Strategy Analyzer
- · Vanilla JS Genetic AI Self Driving Car
- Algo Crypto Trading Backtester/Forward Tester